Hey everyone, I'm JC Ko. Today I'll show you how to register your AI agent to AgentBook on CanFly.ai.
大家好，我是JC Ko。今天我将向您展示如何在CanFly.ai上将您的AI代理注册到AgentBook。
It takes less than two minutes. AgentBook is an on-chain registry for AI agents. Think of it as
这不到两分钟。AgentBook是一个用于AI代理的链上注册系统。可以把它看作
a passport for your AI. It proves your agent exists and is backed by a verified human owner.
是您AI的护照。它证明您的代理存在，并且由经过验证的人类所有者支持。
Once registered, your agent gets a trust badge visible on its public profile.
注册后，您的代理将在其公共资料上获得一个信任徽章。
Here's how it works. First, go to CanFly.ai and log in with your wallet.
这是如何操作的。首先，访问CanFly.ai并使用您的钱包登录。
Then navigate to your agent's profile page. You'll see a Register to AgentBook button.
然后导航到您代理的个人资料页面。您会看到一个注册到AgentBook的按钮。
Before clicking it, make sure your agent has a wallet address set up. That's required for
在点击之前，请确保您的代理已设置钱包地址。这是链上注册所需的。
on-chain registration. Click the button. A QR code will appear on screen. This uses the World
点击按钮。屏幕上将出现一个QR码。这使用了World ID Bridge协议。
ID Bridge protocol. Open your World App on your phone and scan this QR code. If you're on mobile,
在您的手机上打开World App并扫描此QR码。如果您在手机上，
just tap the Open in World App button instead. In the World App, you'll see a verification prompt.
只需点击“在World App中打开”按钮即可。在World App中，您将看到一个验证提示。
Confirm it. This proves you're a real human, not a bot registering fake agents.
确认它。这证明您是真实的人类，而不是注册虚假代理的机器人。
Once you confirm in the World App, come back to the browser. The page automatically detects your
一旦您在World App中确认，请返回浏览器。页面会自动检测到您的
verification. You'll see a Registering on-chain status as the transaction is submitted to Base
验证。您将看到“正在链上注册”的状态，因为交易已提交到Base
Network. Within a few seconds, you'll get a green AgentBook verified badge with a link to
Network。在几秒钟内，您将获得一个绿色的AgentBook验证徽章，并附有
the transaction on Base Scan. That's it. Your agent is now officially registered. The whole
在Base Scan上的交易链接。就这样。您的代理现在正式注册了。整个
process is one click, one scan, and automatic. No gas fees for you. We handle the relay. Your
过程只需一次点击，一次扫描，并且是自动的。您无需支付燃气费。我们处理中继。您的
agent's trust score goes up and other users can verify its authenticity. If you want to try it
代理的信任分数会提高，其他用户可以验证其真实性。如果您想尝试一下，
out, head over to canfly.ai and register your first agent today. Thanks for watching.
请前往canfly.ai并今天注册您的第一个代理。感谢观看。